A Guide to the Papers of the McGill-Mahone Families
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Excursion ticket 1854 Jul 4 (Box 7)
- Clippings 1859 (Box 7)
- Business and Political Correspondence of General William Mahone 1867 Oc. (Box 7)
- Correspondence of William Mahone - Business and Political 1867 Nov. (Box 7)
- Clippings 1860 (Box 7)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone - Political 1867 Dec. (Box 7)
- Clippings 1861-1862 (Box 7)
- Lynchburg Virginian, 1 page 1864 Feb 19 (Box 7)
- Lynchburg Virginian, 1 copy 1864 Aug 26 (Box 7)
- Lynchburg Virginian, 1 page 1864 Oct 8 (Box 7)
- Disbursements and Receipts, weekly - Richmond Whig1868 Aug - Dec (Box 7)
- Statement of Receipts - Richmond Whig1868 Aug 15 - 1871 Jan 1 (Box 7)
- List of employees; Sevices performed and weekly allowances - Richmond Whig[1868] (Box 7)
- Letter on Richmond Whig- RV Richardson to General William Mahone 1868 Jun 6 (Box 7)
- Memorandum of Agreement on sale of Richmond Whig to John C. Shields 1868 Aug 12 (Box 7)
- C. Shields ( Richmond Whig) to General William Mahone 1868 Aug 31 (Box 7)
- Letters to General William Mahone on Richmond Whig1868 Oct (Box 7)
- Correspondence 1868 Oct (Box 7)
- Letters from Richmond Whig to General William Mahone 1868 Oct - Dec (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, personal, political, Business Insurance Table n.d. (Box 7)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1868 Jan - Jun (Box 7)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1868 Jul - Sep (Box 7)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1868 Nov - Dec (Box 7)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 4 folders 1869 Jan - Apr (Box 8)
- Richmond Whig and Advertiser 1869 Apr 9 (Box 8)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1869 May (Box 8)
- Disbursements and Receipts by weeks, Richmond Whig1869 Jan - Dec (Box 8)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 5 folders 1869 Jun - Dec (Box 8)
- Richmond Whig Statements 1870 Jan - Mar, May - Dec (Box 8)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 2 folders 1870 Jan - Sep (Box 8)
- Papers and Correspondence of General William Mahone 1871 (Box 8)
- Monthly Statements - Richmond Whig1871 Jan - Nov (Box 9)
- N. B. Meade to General William Mahone n.d. (Box 9)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1871 Aug - Dec (Box 9)
- Richmond Whig's monthly statements 1872 Jan - Mar (Box 9)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 4 folders 1872 Jan - Dec (Box 9)
- J. A. Walker to General William Mahone - Politics and Railroad [1872] (Box 9)
- N. B. Meade to General William Mahone [1872-1873] (Box 9)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 3 folders 1873 Jan - May (Box 9)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 7 folders 1873 Jun - Dec (Box 10)
- Printed material 1873 (Box 10)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence [1873] (Box 10)
- Advertisement for furniture [1873-1874] (Box 10)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 5 folders 1874 Jan - May (Box 10)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 7 folders 1874 Jun - Dec (Box 11)
- Printed material 1874 (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence of General William Mahone [1874] (Box 11)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 5 folders 1875 Jan - May (Box 11)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone, 7 folders 1875 Jun - Dec (Box 12)
- Miscellanous Correspondence of General William Mahone [1875] (Box 12)
- Clippings 1875 (Box 12)
- Tiffany and Co. to General William Mahone 1876 Jan 17 (Box 12)
- R. W. Hughes to General William Mahone 1876 Oct. 10 (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1884 Jan (Box 12)
- Inge and Mahone Trust in account with Joseph S. Budd, Trustee 1884-1885 (Box 12)
- Accounts: N. M. Osborne with Bolling and Brydir 1884 Aug 15 (Box 12)
- Resolution of a Pittsylvania Political Convention [after 1884] (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1885 Jan, Mar, Aug, Sep, Dec (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1886 Jul - Dec (Box 12)
- Printed material 1886 (Box 12)
- Note 1886 (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1887 (Box 12)
- Committee Chairman Blanks - Republican State Executive Committee of Virginia 1888 (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1889 (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone [1889] (Box 12)
- Broadside: Special Round Trip Excursion rates for Conventions, Conferences and Meetings 1890 Feb 1 (Box 12)
- Papers of General William Mahone 1890 (Box 12)
- Letter from James Bryant to John McGill of Petersburg, Virginia 1890 Feb 28 (Box 12)
- Material in the Government Printing Office 1890 (Box 12)
- Re: Virginia Bond Holders Committee ca. 1890 (Box 12)
- 5 Maps of Mineral Deposits on R.R. lands ca. 1890 (Box 12)
- Broadsides 1890 (Box 12)
- Papers on Mineral deposits on properties situated in Tazewell County 1890-1891 (Box 12)
- Charts showing coal and iron in Tazewell Co. - Sites - Valves - Properties [1890-1891] (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1891 May (Box 12)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1891 Jun - Dec (Box 13)
- Campaign Statements [ca. 1891] (Box 13)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1892 (Box 13)
- Clippings 1892 (Box 13)
- Public Resolution No. 15 1892 June 6 (Box 13)
- General William Mahone account with J. G. Walls 1893 (Box 13)
- General William Mahone account with J. G. Walls 1893 (Box 13)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1893 (Box 13)
- Deeds Nos 1 - 30 1893 (Box 13)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone n.d. (Box 13)
- Notebooks - Copies of correspondence, etc. n.d. (Box 13)
- 5 Maps showing Mahone properties in Washington, DC ca. 1893 (Box 13)
- Printed material 1893 (Box 13)
- Clippings 1893 (Box 13)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1894 Jan - Mar (Box 13)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1894 Jun - Dec (Box 13)
- Printed material, clippings, etc. 1894 (Box 13)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone [1894] (Box 13)
- Correspondence of General William Mahone 1895 (Box 13)
- Correspondence to Capt. Asa Rodgers 1895 July (Box 13)
- Printed material 1895 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous, etc. [1895] (Box 13)
- A Bill to Provide for the Proper Registration of Electors, and the Proper Conduct and Return of all Elections [1895] (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous n.d. (Box 13)
- Clippings n.d. (Box 14)
- Blueprints of Washington, D.C. property ca. 1893 (Box 14)
- Maps of Washington properties ca. 1893 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Printed Materials n.d. (Box 14)
- List of hospitals; removed from Letter Book A 15 ca. 1912-1913 (Box 14)
- Receipt, Letter, Inventory; removed from Journal B5 ca. 1912-1913 (Box 14)
- Printed clipping, order form and note; removed from Ledger B 7 ca. 1838 (Box 14)
- Account of the estate of Robert Leslie, J. McGill executer; removed from Journal/Ledger/Register of Bonds B 19 page 47 1887 (Box 14)
- Notes; removed from Journal B 27 1895-1899, n.d. (Box 14)
- Balance Sheet; removed from Journal B 28 1906 (Box 14)
- Invoice notes; removed from Ledger B 30 1913, n.d. (Box 14)
- Check, Balance sheet, notes; removed from Checkbook B 36 1918, ca. 1916-1919 (Box 14)
- Notes; removed from Notebook C 2 1878-1879 (Box 14)
- Notes; removed from Notebook C 3 1887 (Box 14)
- Notes; removed from Notebook on English language C 4 1888 (Box 14)
- Notes; from Notebook C 6 1887 (Box 14)
- Notes; removed from Notebook C 8 1878-1879 (Box 14)
- Notes; removed from Notebook E 8 1887 (Box 14)